Are you ready to sack?
Crefice the Isaac.
Because I am.
We're gonna offer him up to the gods.
We will pull off his limbs one by one.
We will cut out his tongue.
Scrape out his eyes and boil them in oil.
This is the sound of his blood dripping.
As I empty his body.
Haha, I am mean.
I'm a real bastard.
He's a child?
Well...
It's called the suffering of Isaac for a reason, right?
Oh, yeah.
I'm drinking iced tea.
In case you're curious.
Your first dream.
How is that true though?
You don't have a first time message.
Hmm.
Unless you wrote something earlier that I missed.
What's up, Beth?
Good to have you.
No cracking later today.
Cracking?
Oh, you mean like...
I mean the coke?
No, no, no.
Not today.
Let's go.
Let's play some Isaac.
We have a crazy streak going right now.
At least for my standards.
The streak is...
I actually forgot.
Was it five?
It's five.
Wow!
Guys, I have never been over two.
And this is like a five now.
Or maybe was it three.
It's time.
The question is...
Who's it gonna be?
Kinda wanna do Jacob and Esau again.
But that is kinda...
You know...
That's putting the streak at risk here.
Wow, we have a lot of completion marks on Bethany.
Apollyon has almost none.
And I gotta be honest.
I kinda forgot what he does.
We also have these characters, obviously.
That we could do things on.
Judas.
Shadow Eater.
Azazel.
I mean...
Wait.
Whoops.
Wrong button.
Let's just...
The poop?
Oh, this is the guy.
Right.
I guess I could do that.
Bethany...
I mean, Apollyon!
It's gotta be Apollyon.
And we haven't even killed Isaac.
That's the...
That's the mission.
So that means we gotta get...
Uh...
The picture, and then we go up.
That's how that works.
La la...
La la la la...
Let's see if I remember this.
Okay, so this guy has...
A void.
Consumes any pedestal items in the room, and triggers the effects of all previously consumed active items.
Right.
Any pedestal items in the room.
Okay.
Consuming a passive item grants a permanent stat boost.
I like that one.
Consuming an active item permanently adds its activation effect to Void's activation effect.
Okay.
Got it.
I think.
Uh, maybe I don't...
Hold on.
So right now it doesn't do anything.
Not yet.
Hold on, I gotta move my mouse pad.
It's in the way.
That's my coffee mug.
There we go.
What is this?
Mucormycosis.
Chance to fire fungus shots that stick to enemies.
When attached, fungus shots grow to a certain size and explode into a damaging poison gas cloud.
So this is a passive item.
I'm going to consume it.
Wait, so we didn't get the stats.
No, we got the stats, but we didn't get the...
The effects?
That's good though.
Keep getting stats.
Stats are good.
I'm happy with that.
May have been a wrong decision.
I'm not sure.
I feel good about it though.
Do you feel good about it?
Dude, I feel like I'm in the zone today.
Oh, nice.
Got a key.
Sup, dude.
And a bomb as well.
What a start.
Ah, shit.
Okay.
Okay, thank God it's the first level.
Hey, dude.
Oi!
Dude, these guys are actually the hardest enemies in the game.
Fucking change my mind.
Uh, shop?
I don't have any money.
Ooh!
Mama Mega!
Imagine we get it out of the void!
Dude, we gotta...
Oh no, I can't even destroy the thing to get money!
It's the re-roll thing!
Aw, shit!
This could be insanity if I get that.
There's no way I'm getting the money for that.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
It says any pedestal in the room.
Um...
Isn't this...
An actum...
Or like, uh...
An item pedestal?
Technically?
Couldn't I just use that right now?
Hold on.
I'm not gonna do it yet.
Okay, you're gonna jump at me.
That's fine.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
How you going?
Okay, boss is here.
Ah...
Should I...
Oh, man.
Okay, fine.
Do the boss.
It's Larry.
Gotta kill one of them at least.
A little fast.
Wow.
What's happening?
Oh, I gotta make a path here.
Nice.
Hey!
Beautiful!
Matchbook!
I should've consumed it.
Damn it.
I misplayed.
I did.
I could've had stats instead of that crap.
I guess one black heart is a nice buffer for the next stage here.
And you know what?
I'm gonna go buy the blue heart too.
And I'm gonna try to use this active in there just to see.
Because I don't remember what it actually did in here.
It doesn't do anything.
Now we know.
Two buffers is great.
Also, wait a minute.
Any destructible rocks maybe?
Perhaps a secret room?
Right here.
Let me check the other rooms first.
Yep.
Definitely.
Huh?
Okay, I know where it is.
No, I don't.
Okay, wait.
I know where it is.
Easy.
Wait, I don't.
I know where it is.
Wait, I don't because that one is a narrow room.
Wait, hold on.
What?
Okay, I am actually so lost.
Uh...
Oh...
No, wait.
No.
No, I have no idea.
I got no clue.
That seemed impossible.
Like, it doesn't even make sense.
The question though.
Angels or demons?
I think we're going for angels.
But who knows?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This room is crazy.
I don't know how I'm not getting hit yet.
Fucking hell.
Wow!
I freaking nailed that.
Somehow.
I have actually evolved to the next level.
Uh-oh.
Go!
Drive-by.
But we have the buffer for a reason.
This one's gonna be a tough one.
Maybe.
Dude, they're going faster and faster.
Good thing we have some maneuverability in here.
Okay.
It's a bomb up there.
I guess that means I can just destroy this.
Key and coin.
Coin.
I got two keys.
I'm not going to use it on this.
Not yet.
Get him!
Okay.
I think the whole trick to this guy is I have to use my active in a really, really smart way.
I can't be making stupid plays with that.
I need to nail it, you know?
Wait, what just happened there?
Yeah, bomb me!
Bomb me!
Yes!
Hey!
Good.
Apollyon.
This way.
Oh, God.
Oh!
Wow!
Okay, we have an item room.
Get ready.
Only smart plays.
With the active.
Don't be an asshole.
Uh...
Hold on.
I need to read this again.
Consumes the pedestal item.
Triggers the effects of all previously consumed.
Activite.
Right.
Okay.
Consuming a passive item.
Grants.
You know what?
I don't care about little Gish.
Yeah!
I meant to use it on it!
How
on earth is that possible?
I swear to God, that is just...
I had a brain fart, man!
I was decided I was gonna use the active on it!
Shit!
God dammit.
It's not actually that bad.
I mean, I guess the familiar isn't too bad.
It's okay.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
We wanna do this boss now, while we still have...
Uh...
Buffer.
Yeah.
Hey, look!
We have a healing in here!
Ow!
Oh!
Okay.
Are they gonna charge me or something?
Oh!
There he comes.
Whoa!
Calm down.
Squeezy, let me think!
Tears two souls...
I think I want this.
I'm not gonna...
Active...
This...
Wait a second.
Yo!
What if I active...
Demon items?
Wait a sec.
Consuming... That should work?
Right?
Tears... I mean, I like this.
I'm taking this, and then I'm gonna use this in here.
But wait, how's it gonna... Is it gonna choose one for me, or...?
Rinse.
No, I don't... Oh!
Yo!
Getting this would be sick!
Hold on, I need to read this again.
Any... Any in the room!
Is it gonna consume both?
But wait, that means every time I use the thing... Going forwards, I'm gonna consume or remove one HP.
Forever.
But maybe we focus entirely on blue and black hearts, then.
Honestly, I think we can do it.
Okay, I guess they don't count.
Whatever.
Uh... For the current room...
...Rerange...
Yeah.
I wonder if I have to take it first, and then...
No, I'm not gonna risk it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I actually cannot believe this.
Fucking... That is a pedestal item!
Like, the pedestal may not be there, but that is the pedestal item.
You can't tell me it's not.
I'm going in the double key room now.
And we're gonna get good items.
Whoa!
Okay!
Money?
Now I just need a key to get into the shop, and we can potentially buy something amazing.
There's actually a key here I can grab.
I'm gonna do it.
Oh!
That is so lucky!
What the fog?
Oh, wait.
I need a key to get in.
Uh... Odmash...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Damage range.
That is definitely something I do not wanna active.
So I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
Yoink!
Thank you very much.
Very good.
All right, now we go down and explore the other rooms.
Oh, I don't like this.
Actually, I do like it.
Did you see that?
Wait, what happened to...
Hello?
Stop!
Jesus!
Oh!
I'm fine.
Let's go.
But now I don't have a key, so...
Ah...
That's fine.
Man.
I feel like I've misplayed a little bit in this run, so far.
Like, this has not been optimal gameplay.
Got a fight room.
No key, though.
Ooh.
Ah, I can't get that anyway.
Ha!
I had
the key, or the coin appears there.
Uh-oh.
Just stay at range.
Inanimate objects can't hurt you.
I'm rich?!
Come on, son.
What you got?
My-my little guy is slowing them.
I actually like that.
I'm kinda glad that I didn't consume them.
Yeah.
I'm happy.
I feel like the small guys have more HP than the big guys here.
Bomb for me.
Yeah.
The parts are good.
Wow.
Whoa!
Jesus.
Wah!
Dude, I'm getting bombarded from all sides.
Really difficult.
Okay, boss.
What was that sound?!
Oh, it was the sound of the boss, but he did it weirdly in the loading screen.
That's definitely a bug.
Watchy.
Wait, should I even focus the little guys?
Maybe I don't care.
Where is he?
Oh my god!
Nice.
That was good damage.
Ah!
We can't get hit.
Oh, thank god.
Yo, that is a great item.
I cannot be consuming that.
I can't.
I need it.
We got good damage now.
This is nothing to scoff at.
I kinda need some buffers here.
Wait, I can't get in there.
That is impossible without flying.
George!
I was a little stuck.
Very nice.
Maybe we consume item now.
Let's see.
Oh, I almost used the key on the box.
Imagine.
Replaces tears with eyeball shots that can bounce off of each other.
Eyeball shots not limited by range.
I don't like this one, actually.
Fuck this.
We get speed and luck.
Not a big fan of that.
I think the trait was pretty even.
But I guess a little speed is nice.
Justice.
I like that one.
Okay, let's see.
We got booster pack.
Ugh, I don't like that very much.
Pill.
This pill could be a health up.
Hmm.
I'll save my money.
I could donate, but I'm saving.
I gotta maintain my streak, you know?
I put everything into every run now.
No expenses spared.
Yeah, you can have that bomb.
Wait, he can drop a pedestal item.
And then I can consume it.
Oh my god, I'm using all my bombs.
Come on!
One more!
Oh my god, what a waste!
That was terrible.
Really unlucky.
Still can't open that.
Wait, they're stuck in there!
Huh!
What a weird room.
Beautiful!
Okay, so we've been here.
Let's go this way.
Was it close?
Nope.
I mean, what can I do?
Hoi yo yo!
Oh, I almost ran into that.
I think we have some healing.
I think there's more healing somewhere.
Oh, there we go.
What was this?
I think we may be done here.
Now to remember how to get out.
Not here.
I think it was down south somewhere.
Nope.
Wait, where the hell...
Was it up here?
God, I hate this deep buff of not seeing the map.
It's just the worst.
Uh...
No buffer, unfortunately.
No buffer.
Oh, oh no.
This one is so difficult.
Somehow we did it!
Without taking any damage.
I'm impressed with myself.
Whoa!
Playing it kind of close here with no buffer.
How did he die?
That was an insane shot.
Uh, man, I need keys real bad.
Wow, I can't do anything in here.
I can get this bomb?
That's so sad.
Threading the needle.
Why are you small?
I'm gonna wait for them to come to me.
We're playing it safe here.
Trying to maintain.
Also, I need a shot.
And a key!
This room is gonna kill me.
This seems absolutely impossible.
Yeah, I don't know what to do in there.
This is just...
Too much crap in too little room.
Unfortunate.
Still no key.
Dude, I am suffering.
With this lack of keys.
Oh!
I may die here!
Fuck!
Kill him!
Jesus Christ!
Get that HP.
We got a key.
Okay, where do we use it?
It's gotta be the shop, right?
Oh...
Oh, oh, oh!
Uh...
Creates...
No...
No, I hate that one.
Uh...
I don't like this shop!
We can buy a key.
I'll take that.
I'll take this as well.
Uh...
That's about it.
Wait, what I could do...
No, no, no.
Leaving.
We're gonna go open up the item room now.
Marked!
Tears automatically fire at a crosshair on the ground.
Controlled by...
I don't like this one.
We're gonna consume it.
Damage and...
Uh...
Shot speed.
Fuck yeah.
Very good.
Oh, oh!
Artillery.
Another key!
That's huge!
That means we can now open a chest here.
Uh...
Maybe I'll save it a little bit and come back.
Who knows what we'll find.
Ooh!
That guy came at me at Mark 9!
Line him up!
I ran into it.
Oh, there's Fatty down there.
What's up, Fatty?
Disgusting.
Well, we already lost demon chance, so...
Wait, this is like the ideal...
I believe so much, I'm gonna do it.
What did I tell you?
This is the key master.
Hmm...
No thanks.
Go to hell.
Chance to gain a random passive mushroom effect.
Do I want that?
Or do I wanna keep my matchstick?
Uh...
Nah.
Ah!
Actually, yeah.
Since I have so much damage, maybe it'll amplify with the effects that it gives me.
Could be kinda cool.
Also, I have three keys now, so...
Bomb that.
Oh!
Nah.
I can't use my last two keys on that, that's too much.
Ah!
Fucking skeletons.
Why are skeletons the worst enemies in all games?
Okay.
I may activate the magician here.
Yeah, I'm gonna do it.
Oh my...
God...
What is hitting me?
What the fuck am I getting hit by?
Can we get a replay on that?
I don't understand...
Fucking streak is over just like that.
I have no idea what just happened!
Why did I get hit like four times in a row?
No!
It makes no sense!
Meh, that's stupid!
I hate it!
That pissed me off!
Now I'm upsetting spaghetti!
What a bullshit way to die!
I'm going east.
I have no idea what just happened!
That's like the worst part.
Not knowing what just occurred.
What's that?
Uh...
Yeah, okay.
I'll take it.
I could blow up these fires and potentially get a blue heart.
Well, now that we don't have a streak anymore, let's just fucking YOLO it.
No more safe gameplay.
We're going hard.
Nothing to lose.
Speed run!
Bro, how much HP do you have?
Gimme.
Did we get an item room?
We did.
Okay, we're going.
Fuck it!
Go!
Oh my god.
Just... be patient.
Nice!
Sponsor, red heart, key bomb, coin pill card, and a trinket on...
Boo!
Consume!
Oh!
Nice, we got ranged.
Okay.
Go!
I saw what happened at the end.
I got shoop-de-whooped, because that's one of my actives now.
That's right.
Speed run!
That was almost a corner situation.
Get in.
These are like anti-speed run rooms.
If you get these, there's just nothing you can do about it.
Like,
it takes forever.
Finally.
I think I heard a key as well.
Like, this room is going to take 10 years as well.
Ahhhh!
Man.
Money right before the shop, huh?
Not bad.
Not when I can't see what it is.
Oy, oy, oy.
There's another key somewhere that I forgot.
Back here.
How the fuck?
I'm so bad.
Is that the one I think it is?
That's the one.
That is the one.
Wonderful.
What an item.
Now we gotta get more bombs.
There we go.
We're still speed running though.
Stop spawning them.
I gotta...
I gotta play it safe sometimes.
Okay.
Why did I go in here?
We're going boss.
Go.
Speed!
Yeah, heal me, heal me.
Yeah.
Yeah, we love that.
We love the bombs.
I don't even care if I'm getting hit.
Hit me all you want.
Hit me, hit me.
Come on, hit me.
Hahaha.
Let's die.
Okay.
Okay, I guess.
Speed!
Maybe it's full speed run today now.
Plans have changed.
Full speed on every run.
Oh god.
Oh my...
Hot...
Ah...
Tjahaha!
Hoi yoi yoi.
Shit.
Stop spotting these little...
Bastards.
Wow.
Proptosis.
Tears can enlarge...
Much shorter range.
Actually, I like that with the bomb setup.
I like that.
Sick.
Wait, why did I just do that?
Just blow the thing up!
Huh?
Wait, that...
Wait, I'm confused.
I don't know what's happening.
Oh god.
Oh!
Speed...
Honestly, that's not bad either!
I'll take it!
We're speedrunning.
That is just...
Not great.
But hey!
We're on good time right now.
We're doing great on time.
I don't know why I get one shot here.
Shouldn't they hit me for half a health?
I just don't understand.
I really don't understand.
Thanks.
Like, I don't understand why I took a full health damage there.
From one shot.
Makes no sense to me.
I thought you only took one full health of damage when you reach the womb.
I guess I'm wrong.
It happens on floor...
Whatever that floor was.
Four or something?
Three.
Faster, faster, faster!
This way.
What the fuck?
That was such an unfortunate way to end that run.
I had the best setup ever.
Honestly, it was also so unfortunate that I got the health down pill.
Can't really prepare for something like that.
It just... you know.
I got fucked by RNG.
No cope.
There's one more.
Suck on that.
I'm gonna cheese strategy this guy.
Cheese config coming up.
Almost had it.
Almost had it!
Shit.
There we go, baby!
What'd you get, dude?
Oh, he got out of it.
Here we go.
This is the perfect cheese.
Matchbook.
No!
I consume.
And I resume.
Useless room.
Fast, fast, fast.
I think we are really good on...
What is this room?!
This guy jumped 10 kilometers!
Bro, I've had it.
I fucking had it with this character.
No more.
Full speed.
I don't give a shit anymore.
I need to gain some confidence back.
I don't give a shit.
Nope.
Don't care.
Why would anyone play any other character?
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Fast!
Gimme!
Speed!
Fucking shoot the laser, you idiot!
There was also a rock in there.
Oh, I can fly, that's right.
Go, go, go, go, go!
No, I have no bombs.
Okay.
See ya!
Guy also has a laser.
I'll take that.
Go!
Full send!
Two of clubs, die, uh, sure.
Hearts, sure.
Full, yeah.
Man, my charge up is slow right now.
69, nice.
I feel so protected.
Why do I always get the best items whenever I play this fucking character?
Like, it's every time.
Yeah!
Faster!
Thank you.
We don't stop for nothing.
Go, go, go!
We're doing secret room on the next floor.
Screw, I'll take it.
I'm definitely doing this.
Contract from below, uh...
Yeah.
Sure.
Go!
I don't even know what my plan is.
We're going as deep as we can.
As fast as we can.
Good.
Gimme, gimme.
I'm not fast enough.
There's one more.
Look how fast I'm going, man!
That's gonna kill me.
I can't take those.
Fucking hell.
Now I could've.
Oh my god!
The faster I go, the less time I have to think, the better I play.
Can't overthink anything.
Uh, south.
Uh, yeah, go.
No, we don't have time.
We do have time.
Speed run strats.
Dude, where's this boss at?
What the hell?
Hey, this character is just broken on so many levels.
Wait, is this like a double trouble?
What the hell is that?
D7?!
Respawns all enemies in the room and rewards can be earned again?
What?!
Hell yeah, that sounds cool.
Uh, you know what?
Donate all the money.
Who needs money?
On this character?
No.
There you go.
Fully donated.
Dude, where the...
I feel like I have gone the worst path ever for speed running.
Good thing I made some good time in the beginning.
Throw them up.
So I wonder if I can do this room again.
That's like the first thought I had.
Wow, he's already dead?
How the...
Fuck?
It didn't do anything in this room.
Oh!
Maybe I should have used it in the next room.
Uh...
No.
Brimstone bombs.
I'll take this.
I'll also take this.
Thank you.
Go!
This is doing wonders for my confidence right now.
This is bringing me back on the right mental track.
You know?
Experimental pill.
Two range down is pretty bad for me.
I'm not gonna lie.
That's... that's a devastating hit.
What the hell is going on here?
I'm trying this.
And I got some battery out of it?
Do it again.
Do it again!
I love this room!
I can't get enough of this room!
Again!
Dude, what the...
What is this item?
Okay, let's not do it again.
I've had enough of this room now.
No more of that room.
Nope, we're not doing that.
Faster.
Here we go!
Loki!
Dude, it's not going too well.
Uh... no.
Do it again!
Oh my god!
You fucking asshole.
Thanks.
I don't even know what's happening, honestly.
At this point, I'm just going with the flow.
What's up, mom?
What are you doing?
Get in here.
What the hell?
Yeah, I'll take this.
Never seen something like that.
Oh man, my HP situation is looking grim.
Oh!
I ran into something!
The fuck?
Well, that was very dramatic.
I think this could be over before we know it.
Ex-lax.
I need health!
Health!
This is not what I need.
Come on!
Come on, health up!
Shit.
Cool.
I'm going.
I don't care.
I am in trouble here.
Oh, well.
Oh, right!
We have that!
Go again!
Oh my god, my shot didn't land.
Fuck you, mom.
Let's try that a third time.
Come on.
There we go!
Third time's the charm.
We're taking this one.
We're taking...
That one.
We're going in here.
Host hat.
Hey, I like that.
Wait, I forgot I had to choose.
There was probably something else in here.
Oh well.
We have a hat now.
Wait, so wait.
I'm immune to explosions, right?
Yeah.
That's actually not bad.
Especially against this guy.
But having one HP in here is...
You know, it's a little...
A little questionable.
This guy better spawn some black hearts for me.
Brother.
Brother, brother, brother.
Okay.
I've got my confidence back, though.
That's all I needed.
I'm happy now.
I think it's time we try the, uh...
The other Azazel here.
We gotta go for...
Satan on this guy.
This is the new plan.
Wow.
Kind of a good start.
Actually a really good start.
Finding planet.
Wait, tears?
Hmm.
Hey!
I don't mind that.
Wait.
I hate that.
I am not a big fan of that.
For a second I was like, Oh yeah, I'm playing Azazel, which means good...
Range is good for me.
But this is the Azazel that has infinite range.
So...
Yeah.
That happened.
You know what?
We start over!
Fuck that!
Fuck that noise.
That's right.
There's no way I'm gonna play with that.
That's just gonna be miserable for...
A long time.
Free lemonade!
You know what?
Oh, I can't get it!
Ah...
I have to remember I can't fly.
Oh yeah!
That felt good.
Man, it's so satisfying killing them with this effect.
Uh...
No...
Was that a treasure...
That was a treasure room over there.
Guess we're speedrunning!
Did I just push him away?
Wow!
What a speed!
Actually insane.
I had no idea you could just do that when he came charging at you.
I'd definitely change this direction.
Ah!
Piss it!
Shit.
Ah!
Kill it!
I'm okay.
Just have to get some aggression out.
Oh, uh...
Yes, dude!
Worth...
Oh my god, the damage is crazy!
We're not doing demons.
But we are doing, uh, treasure rooms.
Yeah!
Dude, I'm getting good at this.
I didn't mean to go in here.
I didn't mean to go in there.
This really fucked me now.
That just cost me the run.
Going in there.
That was actually satisfying.
Oh, wait, what?
More enemies?
Ah...
Come on, be something good!
Alright, that's decent.
11 coins as well.
Yep!
That's what we need.
I'm gonna donate.
I have a feeling this run is about to end in a second here.
You know what the good news is?
We're donating a lot, right?
So...
Maybe we can reach a thousand today if we...
...have shitty runs and we just keep donating.
I guess that's a strategy.
Uh...
No.
Angels!
I feel like I'm on a downward spiral.
Mentally.
Just slightly.
Come on, this is a health up!
Okay.
Not quite.
This guy needs to calm down.
Oh, that's so cruel!
That is so cruel!
Oh, I have to remember I can use this ability to...
...block shots!
That's a thing.
That is actually such a badass ability.
Uh, alright.
We just need some red hearts now.
Oh god.
Shit!
But...
Dude, I'm fucked!
Oh my...
God.
Man, I have no money.
Oh, it's such a good run.
I don't wanna lose it!
Fuck.
Oh, it's this guy as well.
It is absolutely over.
Oh, yo!
Wow!
Don't die!
Oh!
Fucking...
Hell!
Holy shit!
Yes!
Angel Clutch!
Bring around Isaac?
Chance to reflect?
It's not great.
I'll...
I'll take it.
I will blow you up for what you've done to me.
Suck on that.
Oh god!
Dude, I'm nailing this guy.
Oh ho!
You got owned!
Holy shit!
Thanks.
B-b-b-b-b...
Do-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de...
Yeah.
Go.
I'm happy.
We got this.
We got this!
That plus one health...
...really refueled my...
My mental...
Like, how good is that?
Yeah, I mean, I mean, I mean, what are you gonna do?
Fucking skeletons.
We gotta get more HP.
Like, more red hearts.
That's what we need.
I hate being lost.
Oh no, this room is ass!
Oh, that's huge!
We're coming back for that.
Uh-oh.
Whoa!
What is... Oh, it's my shield that's deflecting it.
I see now.
This leech is gonna start to pay for itself very soon.
Uh... Yeah, actually!
That's really nice!
Oh, that's a friend.
I'm getting better.
Wait, scissors?
No!
I hate that.
Butthole?
Oh, belly button.
Uh... Yeah.
Partridge.
Okay.
And that was that up there.
Bro, I'm not gonna be able to find my way out before...
My chance of speedrunning runs out.
Ugh.
What's up here?
No.
What's this one?
Oh my god.
Here?
Here we go.
Not bad.
Uh, don't go in there.
Man, where is this boss?!
Losing my mind?!
Maybe in here?
Not up here.
Tell me this isn't a dead end.
Dude, I have no idea!
This...
This fucking speedrun is over now because I can't find my way around!
Oh!
Is it up here?!
Nope!
Here we go!
I'm gonna donate.
That's why I'm poor.
Oh, this is a dead end.
Here we go!
Finally!
Carrion Queen.
I nailed it.
I don't mind getting some attack speed.
Charge up faster.
Dude, range is actually good on this character.
Just a little, uh, close range, you know?
Gonna get a longer range.
I wasn't paying attention to the timer.
I think we're ahead of the timer.
What the...
I should be immune to the red stuff on the floor.
I'm kind of in trouble here.
These guys are tough to hit?
That's mega massive.
Another one.
I fucking ran into a rock!
I hate myself.
Actually, I think I'll keep the...
The other trinkets.
Scapular!
Ooh!
That's a pretty good one.
Massive pickup.
I'm gonna actually do this.
I'm gonna take this one.
And this one.
I think I'll go west.
Man.
Ah, donate.
Full donation.
We will not stop donating until we have a thousand.
I can't hit...
Nothing, cause I'm...
So bad.
Okay.
Monstro.
I fall for that one every time.
Oh
my god.
Decent.
That is sooo huge.
Wow.
We didn't find...
A treasure room yet?
We gotta go get it.
Treasure room.
It's gotta be on the right side.
I mean, there is only one place it can be.
It's not the big one.
For sure.
Oh.
Maybe it is the big one.
As far away as you can get.
Come on, health up.
Damn it.
Little brimstone.
Actually, I'm okay with that.
A little mini-me.
Hey, we charge at around the same time as well.
That's very convenient.
Okay, let's pay attention to the timer.
I think we're still ahead of it.
Despite the...
Disastrous performance in these last two floors.
Nope.
Shit, we're not.
Okay, we gotta haul ass.
Wait, what is the time?
Is it like 20 minutes?
Hold on, we may not have time.
Go!
Ah, the thing is over.
God damn it.
Shit, I don't even know what the goal is now.
I guess to kill Satan?
That's something I haven't done yet.
Go left.
I lost most of my HP there.
Please open your mouth.
Hmm, man, I can't believe I lost that streak.
No!
Don't!
No, I need that one!
There we go.
South, south.
Didn't mean to do that.
Wow!
We got a library though!
Three books as well!
Oh wait, that doesn't mean anything for me, right?
Uh, wait, what?
Am I shooting twice then?
Sometimes?
Don't think so.
Bro.
Yeah, I think that, uh, upgrade is useless for me.
I've never seen that.
I pushed her off the edge.
Bro, just, just end my life.
I'm not gonna have three attempts on this one.
Cause I can't tell what's fucking enemies and who's mine!
Ah, it's over, bro.
Holy shit!
One heart.
It is pretty much over.
T- S- Ah!
Ah!
Wow.
Holy...
Uh-oh.
Oh no, not static enemies!
Saved.
But I can jump, right?
Can't jump over rocks.
Piss!
I can't, I can't.
Dude, we're at f- We were at five, we're almost at minus five now.
Let's do, uh, Isaac on Lazarus.
We haven't done that one yet.
Come here.
Dude, I am, I am fucking mega tilted right now.
What a horrible set of runs today.
I need, Ipecac.
And Pyromaniac.
That, is fun.
Hey.
Thought I told you to die.
I got a treasure room.
Cause I'm seeing red.
Can't see clearly.
Lazarus comes back though, from dying.
Pisces.
Uh, yeah.
Fine, I guess.
I think I saw a...
Tinted rock as well.
Man, it's gonna take a while.
It's like a really easy boss.
Really tanky, really easy.
Like, what are these pathetic jumps he's making?
That's a good item.
Could've picked up the heart as well.
No time.
Nah, I forgot.
And honestly, if I can't survive these levels with two hearts...
I shouldn't be allowed to continue on anyway.
There we go.
Also, why are my tears so big all of a sudden?
Like, I mean, talking physically here.
Did I get something that increases their size?
Maybe it's the knockback?
Oh, tear size.
It was that one.
I'm gonna die, aren't I?
I'm gonna die to spiders.
Not today.
Wait, what happened?
I'm so mystified with these guys.
That's big.
Unfortunately, too late for the buffer.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, I was close.
Fucking got pushed into the door.
Oh!
I thought you did it three times!
You did it four all of a sudden.
One.
Two.
Three.
And a fourth one?
He tried to.
Oh my god, the ultimate cheese config.
No treasure room, though.
What even is this card?
Ah.
Copies the effect of the active.
I haven't had a good active in...
10 runs!
Or something like that.
Show me the good stuff!
Where are you hiding it?
Nah, yeah, okay.
Donate it!
Everything gets donated.
You know what?
Fuck it.
Too bad.
I mean, we already lost demon chance, right?
Ooh, come on.
Oh, it took an HP from me!
Goddammit.
This is torture.
What?
Alright.
I'm leaving this floor.
This floor...
sucks!
Moving on to greener pastures.
At least we haven't died yet and lost our effect.
In fact, I think we still need to do that.
We have to, uh, win without losing...
The...
No, no.
That was way early on.
That was something else.
Nevermind.
I think we already did that.
We had to win the game without, you know, using our...
Passive.
Fuck off.
You know what I'm frustrated with?
With Isaac right now?
Is that I've played this game so much...
But I'm not feeling any improvement in my gameplay.
You know what I mean?
I've just...
I've just plateaued.
At this point.
I'm not getting better at the game.
In fact, I feel like it's getting worse.
Somehow.
The more I play, the harder it gets.
Which is kind of counterintuitive.
It's weird.
Joy!
Man, the knockback, you can really feel it.
The extra knockback, that actually saved me just now.
Yeah, look.
I'm almost keeping them at bay.
Just barely.
Now we go south.
Uh, wait, wait.
Treasure room.
I have no key.
Right.
Wait, why am I getting...
Is that from the rock?
Oh, it is.
I'm getting money from rocks.
That explains it.
I like these rooms.
These rooms make me happy.
Nice.
We're not gonna be afraid of these spikes anymore.
Change man.
Oh my god.
I hate that sound that plays when you...
Meet this guy.
Wait, he didn't do this attack last time?
Look at the knockback I have.
I'm just pushing him all the way to the other side.
Sometimes his little effect on the floor disappears entirely and you don't know where he is.
Damn.
Man, I need HP.
I can't go on like this.
Damage is good though.
Now we just need survivability.
Also, I got 14 coins.
Oh, I can't use the key here.
Gotta use it up here.
Yeah, I don't like this very much either.
Terrible.
If we're lucky, maybe there's a coin in...
Uh, wait a minute.
I thought I saw another poop.
Guess not.
This is just a killer room.
Like, what do you do?
Oh my god!
Come on!
Dimensional baby!
Oh my god, that really helped.
Multi-dimensions.
Good.
oh...
Toy!
Healing!
Hey!
Wow!
We got money now for the shop.
And we have a key.
This could work.
Ideal scenario, there's a health in there and a blue health.
What is this crap?
Alright, I guess I'll donate everything.
$8.99.
I'm leaving.
That was soul-crushing.
Worst shopping experience of all time.
You know, this baby could actually be one of my saviors.
It does amplify damage by a bit, you know?
No!
Fucking shit.
Healing!
At least we have one extra at life.
I need this.
Dog.
Oh.
Come on!
Yeah!
Good enough.
Key bomb.
He wants your keys.
No!
I need my keys!
I don't have any.
Yeah, I mean...
Okay, we get to rest, though.
Walk into my shots, please.
Just make my life easy.
What is that sound?
And where the hell is the boss?
Yeah!
I'm gonna blow these up.
Because I need blue hearts.
Never lucky.
The forsaken... that's how I feel.
Oh yeah, multidimensional baby totally carried that.
HP up is big!
Also, what does it do other than that?
Chance to spawn a heart when taking damage.
Nice.
That's gonna give us a stain.
Let me take a quick leak.
That's why I keep bottles.
Yeah!
Why am I doing this?
Yes!
Got a blue heart.
We're safe.
Never mind!
Too little space!
Too much shit!
Like the tagline on this game.
Yeah, come on!
Multidimensional!
Multidimensional me!
So good.
You know, I'm happy about this multidimensional...
Oh, fucking god.
What a room.
Yep.
900!
A blue candle has appeared!
Whatever that is...
I feel like I've already had that?
Have I not seen a blue candle before?
That doesn't seem new.
This is my strategy.
Stand still, don't move.
It's vision is based on movement.
It's not working out.
There's another boss!
It's mom.
Hey guys, I think we're in trouble.
I just have a feeling, you know.
I think it's looking pretty grim.
That healing was big.
Thank you, bandage.
Gimme!
Grrrrrr!
Why does mom have so much HP?
I used a card.
Fuck you little creatures.
AHHHHH!
We have no...
Mom.
Mom!
Jesus
Christ.
What the hell?
He got...
2 HP.
Come on, man!
Oh yeah, he's a key bomb.
If I stand behind my baby...
My shots are faster.
Dude, that tank is hell!
I don't know what to fucking do, man.
I can't win.
I can't...
Speed run.
I need to get that confidence back up again.
Because I'm all...
I'm at all-time low right now.
We actually don't have time for that.
Nice.
Blighted ovum!
I'm gonna fucking blight your ovum.
I've had enough of your ovum.
The fuck is that sound?
You hear that?
What the hell was that?
Someone said Isaac!
And then you're like...
Sound like mom.
Faster.
Speed!
Not that fast.
I just wanna fight this...
Whatever his name is.
The fat guy.
In the speed run, you know?
Not the lyrium, the other guy.
I forgot his name.
My argument is, it's so early, who cares?
It's either gonna pay off big time, or it's gonna fizzle out.
Cool.
Good.
But it's because we're playing Azazel, you know?
We get all the good items.
We get all the luck in the world.
That was pathetic.
That was ultra pathetic.
Jim.
Trust me.
Ah!
Stupid little...
We need some good luck on... drop on this one.
No, we don't have good luck.
That's too bad.
Rough start.
But hey, look at how fast we are.
Way ahead of the timer.
So at least we're doing good on that front.
I wonder if that book can drop me a black heart.
Yeah!
Do it!
What the f...
Whoa, wait, whoa!
Okay.
I have no idea what this is gonna be, but...
We'll find out.
We're not fast enough.
This is what's wrong.
We need to be faster.
Great.
Tears down, you love it.
Nothing?
Don't!
Just kill him, please.
Hey!
Haha, we got a shoop.
I don't mind a shoop.
Speed or die.
Infested?
Oops.
I don't even question it anymore.
I know what to do.
Miss click.
I'm trying something new today here.
This is very experimental, all of this.
It's a double trouble... thingy.
Thanks.
Uh...
Just to confirm.
Yep, okay.
Because I always wondered, you know?
I wondered.
But now I know for sure.
Definitely worth it.
For that knowledge.
Don't die.
Go.
There we go!
We got some good luck!
Let's abuse this good luck.
And get a nice speedrun going.
It's a good start.
Gimme me.
Wait, there it is again.
Dude, it always happens when I go fast.
Speed up.
Wait a minute.
I heard something to the left.
Is there something going on here?
Maybe in the unexplored rooms?
Oh my god, stop.
Wait.
Shit!
Fuck off!
Dude, I am so fast right now.
Okay, never mind.
I don't know what's happening.
Something's going on here.
I feel like it's happening when I go fast.
Let's go even faster.
Dude, look at my tears.
It's like instantaneous almost.
I can charge this.
Oh my god!
Okay, we needed to calm down a bit anyway.
That speed was too high.
Stupid little fly!
Wait, we don't have time for this.
In fact, there's one thing I haven't tried.
Which is to, uh...
Get to the endgame here.
And like, way faster than...
I've done before, you know?
Maybe something happens if you go ultra-fast.
Like this.
This is like...
Going straight, you know?
B-lining.
There's gotta be some secret with that.
Look how fa- Wait a second!
Did I get two items because I went fast?
Hold up!
I want this.
No wait, I got to choose.
Oh yeah.
I gotta take that one, baby.
Fast!
I actually can't lose now.
This is statistically one of those runs...
Where...
If I lose this...
I think I'm actually legally obligated to uninstall the game.
I think it's in the contract.
Somewhere.
It's in there.
Like, I'm not allowed to play this game afterwards.
Faster.
Ooh, nice money.
Oh, no keys.
That feels bad.
There we go, we got the key.
Uh...
This one.
Donate!
Quick!
Good.
9-11.
Not the skeletons.
Let's go!
Dude, we have such speed right now.
This guy's tough though.
Oh, he socked me in.
Nice!
So fast.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
This is horrible for me, that does nothing!
We don't have any money either, so that's no good.
My damage is lacking.
Like, if I can't instantly one-shot everything, then my damage is lacking.
Wait, something here.
This satanic bible should be the standard layout for every character as soon as you start the game.
I feel like, without it, I just can't win.
Mars.
Dash attack.
Can I?
Wait, I thought I could dash into enemies and damage them?
Wait, let me see.
Oh, I can!
Good.
That's what that effect was.
Kinda cool, honestly.
Equality!
Uh, no thanks.
Fuck off!
Trying to steal my batteries.
I think I'm faster than any other run I've ever done.
Jesus Christ.
You got owned Abaddon.
Yes, I think so.
Very nice.
That is a huge item.
Oh my god.
Toenail!
No thanks.
Oi!
You don't wanna be, uh, too long- too far away.
You gotta be close.
Give me that battery.
Nice.
Faster.
The fuck?
Ha!
He ran into the spikes!
That's incredible.
I'm also gonna run into the spikes.
Uh...
No.
It was tempting.
But let's not.
Holy money.
Let's not forget we're on a speed run.
Tactical, uh, taking damage to deal enemies.
Damage.
That was a terrible sentence.
What was this one?
Damage.
Nice.
This one is...
Chariot.
Actually, yeah, let's go with that one.
Dude, where's this boss?
I'm so unlucky.
Goddamn toenail.
Just can't get rid of it.
Faster, faster.
Why are you not dying?
Thank you.
This satanic bible is sustaining my crazy gameplay.
It's keeping me going.
Get him.
Haha.
Fish in a barrel.
Speed.
The fallen.
Good night.
Belial, we don't care about that.
Ah, too risky.
I don't know my...
Power level.
We are so far ahead of that timer.
We are gonna get the boss.
Goddammit.
I think I'll just get it back.
Ansus.
Chariot ore.
I can't see it.
Oh, this one.
Uh, boss is...
There.
We go.
We ignore the fucking treasure room.
We're trying something new.
Go, go, go.
Bastard.
They always have to hit me with that.
Come on.
Uh, wait, wait, wait.
Uh...
Right, there's no point.
Dead onion?
Uh, we don't care about that.
Camo undies.
On entering each room...
Dude, these are fucking bad.
Am I crazy?
That's like some proper shit.
What a stinker.
Fuck you.
Use this.
Kill this little thing.
Oh god.
There's two of them!
Ah!
Fuck you!
Oh, we got angels now.
Shit!
Jackie!
No!
I can't...
No, no, no.
Jackie!
Fuck!
Nah, man, I'm done.
I've had it.
I've had my fill.
That's enough Isaac.
I'm losing my damn mind today.
Terrible, terrible.
That was horrible.
Wow.
That has to be like the worst day of Isaac I've ever had.
What happened?
Game is too hard, man.
I'm too old.
Game is too fast.
That's pretty much what's happening.
I don't have the reaction times of a 20 year old anymore.
Like I mentioned earlier...
Jackie, you cannot be on the table.
Come here.
Okay, you can be on my lap.
You can sit here.
Man.
There we go.
Jackie is here to calm me down.
Isn't that right?
Jackie is...
I'm holding Jackie like a baby right now.
And she's chilling.
It's about to be feeding time for Jackie.
She needs to eat in 15 minutes.
Okay, you wanna go down again?
Okay.
Sometimes when I'm on the couch, she will jump up.
And she will like put one of her paws on me like slowly.
As if, excuse me sir, mister.
Excuse me.
And then she wants to get up, you know.
And I hold her for a little bit.
And then she gets tired of it.
And then she runs off.
That's the standard Jackie procedure.
Yeah, it's so cute.
Genius friends.
I don't feel like playing greed mode.
It's just not as fun as the main mode.
Well, I say that after this session, but you know.
You know what I mean.
One thing I think, at least, as a not so skilled gamer, Isaac needs.
In my opinion.
Is some more permanent, like, power-ups as time goes on.
At least in my case.
I just don't feel like I'm getting stronger or better at the game as I play along, you know.
You'll win the next run.
Ah...
Maybe.
I like that you say, do a spoiler stream, as if that's gonna help me play better.
It's not.
Like, the thing is...
It's a...
What was the word for that?
It's a bullet-held game, and...
When I go into a room that's just too small, and there's too much shit on my screen...
My mental just cracks.
I can't do it.
You know?
It's just too hard.
And that's okay!
Like...
I'm just not very good at the game.
That's okay.
That happens.
Some games, you know...
Can't be good at them all.
I have thought of playing God of War, but...
Yeah, I don't know.
I heard some pretty shitty things about it.
And some good things.
So I've been kind of, you know...
I've been a little apprehensive about that.
Not shitty at all.
But I heard that you...
Every time there's a puzzle, the game just tells you the solution immediately.
That sounds pretty bad.
Sounds like something I would be really annoyed by.
You know?
Or maybe that's just one of the God of War games.
I don't know.
I haven't played them, obviously, so I don't know.
I can't really say.
Maybe when I play them, I'll change my mind.
I mean, obviously.
You can't judge something without playing it first.
Let me check my achievements, actually.
How many do I have?
I have 251.
Out of 641.
39% achievements.
You said something negative about big AAA game?
You're done, bro.
Yeah, it's over for me.
I had a good run.
Wait till this guy finds out how I feel about Expedition 33.
Hahaha.
Get him!
Have you tried?
Don't starve together.
I have actually tried it.
But very, very little.
It's pretty much completely blind if I were to play it again.
But I know you can collect sticks and you can...
Like, when night comes, there's like shadows that approach your bonfire and stuff.
That's sort of the thing I remember.
But it seemed fun at the time.
I was playing it with someone.
Very, very briefly.
Is it hard?
So difficult?
More difficult than Isaac?
Really?
It didn't seem like that would be such a difficult game compared to Isaac.
But then again, I just played the beginning, so I don't really know.
Like this game, you know how there's like a different path you can take through...
The sewers or whatever it's called?
And then there's also the other, like the mines and stuff?
Dude, I can't even...
I can't even win the normal path!
I can't even do that other...
No way I can do the other thing.
I can't even do the baby mode.
You know?
Noita is so much easier than Isaac.
In my opinion.
But that's because it's just the type of game that I'm better at, I think.
You think Noita is harder?
But that's the thing, right?
People are different.
For me, bullet health, they really just...
I'm not good at them.
At all.
Noita, you can go really slow, right?
You can go really slow.
And you can take out one enemy at a time.
You can really play strategic.
In Isaac, not so much, man.
You get put into a room with enemies, you have to fight him.
Right now.
You know?
There's no running from it.
Rain World is a lot easier than Isaac.
Isaac may be the hardest game I've ever played.
I mean, I know there's strategy in Isaac, but you know what I mean, right?
If you get put into a room, you have to fight your way out.
You can't just leave the room.
You are locked in that room.
Harder than Terraria?
Obviously.
If I said it's the hardest game ever...
Okay, wait a minute, I take it back.
StarCraft II, trying to reach Grandmaster?
Even harder.
Hahaha.
That's a truly difficult one.
Also, will you please try Flash Isaac version?
But why would I play an inferior version in a Flash version that is just smaller and...
...less feature-rich?
That just sounds not fun to me.
I'm trying to understand why you want me to try that.
What's the point?
It's actually harder?
Sounds like I would not enjoy it then.
Haha.
Flash version is hell?
Hahaha.
Damn.
Okay, that sounds bad.
Nostalgia blind?
Yeah, okay.
Who's the hottest boss, in my opinion?
You mean an Isaac?
Uh...
None of them are particularly hot.
Monstro is a top contender for sure.
Or maybe it's Isaac.
Because if you don't find yourself the hottest...
I mean...
How can you find...
...love?
You know?
You gotta love yourself.
First thing.
That's a five-year-old.
Oh my god.
Damn.
Wait, how do you know he's five years old?
Is that actually a thing?
Is Isaac actually confirmed like five years old?
That's actually kind of funny.
Ah, okay.
Edmund confirmed it.
I see.
Dude, that's even worse now with all the lore.
Fuck.
That makes it even more depressing.
Edmund confirms the most random shit like Jacob and Esau are Isaac's balls?
That's not true.
He didn't say that.
And if he did, then he's trolling.
Come on, man.
It's true.
But that doesn't even make any sense lore-wise.
Because if you lose one ball, you can still go on.
You know?
It's only over if you lose both.
You can survive with one ball.
So who's the kidney?
Who represents his kidneys?
He didn't even survive without balls.
Yeah, yes, that's true.
Have a little bag or something.
Actually, no, you don't even need that, I guess.
Maggie seems like a kidney.
Really?
You can't see Isaac's balls, so that's where they went.
Running around the basement just like him.
I don't want to talk about Isaac's balls now that I know he's five years old.
That's kind of fucked up.
What are you doing, Edmund?
Edmund!
Are you okay?
What is this music from?
It's from Persona.
Persona 5.
This one is cold?
I'll tell you.
Have a short rest.
Isaac is based on his trauma, so no, he's not okay.
Wait, actually?
No.
So you're saying Edmund was locked in a chest as a child?
And he had to run through the basement with knives and scissors?
I don't believe that.
Oh, he's a eunuch.
Talked about it on his...
Guys, I don't even know if I can trust anything you're saying right now.
I'm getting major trolling vibes.
This whole conversation has been...
I don't know.
Designed to mess with me.
His parents are very religious.
Aren't many parents religious though?
Especially in America?
A lot of places are really religious.
It's something that I just almost can't even relate to at all.
Feels like such a different world, you know?
No, no more ball talk.
Oh, man.
You know what I wish?
I wish the game wouldn't have had a hard mode.
That it would just be...
Like, there wouldn't be a difficulty slider.
So I wouldn't feel obligated to play on hard mode, you know what I mean?
I don't even know...
Like, how would normal even feel nowadays?
Doesn't even do much hard mode?
What?
Does it make things harder though?
When is the next Minecraft stream?
I don't know.
Maybe tomorrow or the day after or something like that.
Depends when I feel like it, really.
If I know in advance, I'll try to put it on a schedule.
But mostly I'll just go live, you know?
Have you tried playing Claire Obscure?
I have!
It's on my YouTube.
If you stream tomorrow too, I will shit myself.
Well, that's not good.
Then I'm not gonna stream tomorrow.
That doesn't sound good.
I don't want to put you through that.
What you had for lunch?
I actually had the most boring lunch of all time.
Not nourishing, not filling, not good at all.
I had two pieces of toast with some cheese in between.
Nothing else.
Just one piece of cheese between two pieces of toast.
It wasn't even toasted.
It was straight out of the bag.
So I wouldn't even call that a lunch.
More like a, oh shit, I'm feeling a little hungry, but I'm too lazy to make food, you know?
That's very plain, but we all eat like that every now and then.
Yeah, I guess so.
But tonight I'm making chili.
I'm gonna make up for my laziness.
It's gonna be good.
I'm making what I call poor man's chili.
So I don't use minced meat in that, I just use whatever meat I have.
And right now I have sausages.
So I just chop those up in a pan with some garlic and some chili.
And then you put in baked beans actually, not kidney beans, because this is poor man's chili.
When you're poor, you only have baked beans.
So you put that in.
Then you put some cheese in.
You put some...
A little bit of chocolate if you have it.
And in Denmark we usually have chocolate in the fridge to put on bread.
I know it sounds weird, but we do that in Denmark.
So I put a couple slices of that in there.
And then I also put some cinnamon in there.
And that's pretty much it, I think.
And you mix it up good, and you eat it with bread.
Mmm!
So good.
Guys, Mugenics, is that harder than Isaac?
How hard is Mugenics?
It's like XCOM, say no more fam, I'm in.
I freaking love XCOM.
Speaking of, I'm gonna release an episode of that after this.
For those that are following that, it's kind of crazy.
Like, the amount of people who watch the XCOM series compared to...
Let's just say Minecraft, because it's the other end of the extreme.
It's kind of nuts.
You know?
Like, if I make a hundred dollars...
On a...
Minecraft episode...
I make...
Two dollars.
On XCOM.
Isn't that crazy?
The difference.
Yeah.
It's wild.
Ah, then again, I guess the Minecraft episode is also longer, right?
But still.
XCOM is legendary.
Already in my mind, it's a top tier game.
I'm already tempted to...
Rate it like...
I don't know.
Like, really highly.
After playing it.
But...
I will wait until I've played another game first, so I don't have recency bias.
But it's definitely up there.
Apparently there's also soon another game coming, made by X...
XCOM people.
That should be XCOM-y.
And it's like a Star Wars game, I think?
And I love Star Wars!
So I'm totally in!
Hey, what's up?
Day one...
Out of Wilds Watcher.
No backseat gaming.
But I genuinely think you're at the point with Isaac where you're gonna have to...
Have much more fun if you open the books with Chad.
But the thing is...
You don't understand me then, because that's not gonna bring me more fun.
That's not gonna make the game more fun for me, if you guys tell me what to do next.
It's not.
At that point, I would just rather play something else.
You know, and move on.
But I understand what you're trying to say.
I think Mugenics is already in the backlog, isn't it?
It should be.
Oh, it's not!
Damn.
You're right.
Let me add it to my other 339 games.
On the backlog.
There's a lot.
There it is.
Backlog.
Done!
You can see the backlog here, by the way.
Play Hitman.
You know what, actually?
Maybe that is what I play next.
After Isaac.
Maybe that is actually Hitman.
I've seen some gameplay of it, and it looks really fun.
And I think it's gonna be a disaster though, because...
It's a game where you have to sneak around and do stealthy things.
And if you know me, that is like, the thing I'm worst at.
But it's also kind of fun.
You know?
But I really love sneaking around in games.
I wanna be good at it.
I always try to do it, but I always fuck it up.
And it ends up in a shootout.
Talos is gonna be a locally recorded game for sure though.
It's not a game that lends itself well to three hour streams.
It's too much brain work, you know, for three hours.
Definitely just gonna record that offline, when the time comes.
I do know the website backlogged.
I actually had my backlog on there before I decided to make my own.
Because it was really annoying for people to figure out which games I had played on a game, or on a website that supposedly shows people what games you've played.
Because you can't even search your own library.
So that's why I made this the headline on this site.
The search bar is the main thing, it's up top.
So someone can be, have I played X or Y, you know?
Just type it in and immediately, boom.
I still can't believe they haven't implemented that.
It is like the first thing I try to do when I go to someone's backlogged.
You know?
Try to search for a specific game.
Oh, I can't?
What?
Why not?
So weird.
When are you playing Create?
Probably tomorrow or the day after.
I haven't decided yet.
Depends how I'm feeling.
I'm also getting ready to move here in like a week or so.
So I'm slowly packing things into boxes too.
But obviously I'm going to try and stream as much as I can.
Also, I have made sure that the internet is going to be connected and ready the day I move in.
So if I get things set up, we can get going immediately, you know?
Poor Jackie?
Why?
She's going to love the new place.
It's bigger.
She's going to have so much more room to run around and be silly in.
Is it going to have an AC?
No, but I have an AC now!
I have a portable one.
With like a hose that goes out the window with an outdoor unit.
With a little fan on it and shit.
It looks really American.
You know?
Which means it's probably good.
Extra fast internet?
No, it's about the same internet.
I have a thousand thousand, which is quite standard in Denmark, I think, for most people.
Hard for cats to move usually?
Well, it's going to be like 50 meters.
I think she can handle it.
I can literally see where I'm moving outside my window.
I can probably throw a ball if I do it hard enough and hit my other place I'm moving to.
So it's going to be fine.
Yeah, I'm moving in with my neighbors.
It's the same apartment complex, it's just a bigger unit.
That's it.
Because of a bigger unit.
That's why I'm moving.
To have a bit more space.
I don't even have room for a TV right now.
And I would love to have a TV to watch movies on.
You know?
Right now I sit in my couch with my laptop and watch movies.
Which is just...
You know, it's not great.
Kind of doing a disservice to the movies.
Like Nolan intended.
Dude, I actually considered flying to the UK just to watch that movie in IMAX.
Like proper IMAX.
But all my friends bailed.
They don't want to go.
And I don't want to go alone.
Fucking hell.
Did you leave a review about the loudness of the AC?
Oh!
It's not loud at all!
I run it at literally 1%.
So there's a fan speed setting.
And there's a setting called outside quiet or something.
I put that on.
1% fan speed.
It's enough to keep my entire place at one temperature.
It doesn't...
It almost makes no sound at all.
It is really nice.
Probably not worth it anyways.
You don't think so?
It's the first movie ever shot in full IMAX all the way through.
I feel like that sort of thing is dying out, you know?
Maybe if I don't do this I will never get the chance to experience this again.
And I'm a big movie guy, you know?
I love movies.
I feel like it would be a special experience.
Even if the movie sucks, I don't know if it does.
It probably doesn't.
Since it's Nolan, it's usually pretty good, you know?
Even if it does suck, I know it's gonna be pretty to look at.
Every single IMAX shot in Interstellar and Dunkirk and stuff is always breathtaking, you know?
Why did you decide against backporting the new Minecraft version with a mod to risk in case there are bugs?
Yeah, I mean...
This version I'm playing of Create is just meant for this version of Minecraft.
I just don't wanna, you know...
I'm gonna play it as it was intended right now.
Not gonna lie, I've been watching movies on my phone.
Will Nolan kill me?
No, he won't actually!
Because I saw an interview with him where someone asked him this exact question.
Where they said, is it a crime to watch movies on your phone?
And he said, no.
It's not.
You're good, bro.
Sight viewing?
Wait, what?
Sight viewing at movies.
What's that mean?
But are the IMAX shots breathtaking if it's every shot?
I guess.
I think so.
A crime is watching a movie in 1.5 speed.
You are so right.
I had a friend.
His name was Peter.
He would... I'm not even kidding.
Like, he was watching Game of Thrones.
He would, like, skip through sections.
He would just be like, nah, I don't wanna watch this part.
I'm gonna go forwards until I see this character again.
And, honestly, man, I almost cut off communication with him after hearing that.
That's just...
That's a crime right there.
Like, he doesn't understand, you know?
The way of the movie and the shows.
You can't do that.
Yeah, if you don't like the movie, then just stop it.
Don't watch it.
Don't skip through it.
That's just... I don't know.
That's a crime.
Remember when it comes to watching movies at home, the sound is more important than the screen?
Is it?
I've never had, like, surround sound in my home before.
I mean, I've heard it at the movies, and it's great, sure.
But I do love a good screen.
But, obviously, if you have, like, laptop speakers, it's horrible.
That's why I use headphones while I watch movies.
Headphones are...
So good.
What do you think about people that split a movie into two viewing sessions?
It's okay.
I mean, sometimes you gotta stop and do something else, you know?
You get interrupted or whatever.
Or maybe you get bored and like, Oh, I gotta do something else or come back.
I think it's okay.
But it depends a little, I guess.
You're playing on a laptop?
No, no, no, I'm playing on my desktop here.
It is like, my desktop computer is like the one item I own in real life that is like worth a lot of money, you know?
It's the one thing I invest in.
I don't have a car, I don't have a TV, I don't even have anything, like, super extravagant at all.
But my computer, the one I play games on, you best believe I upgrade that!
That's where my money goes, you know?
I don't go drinking on the weekends, at least very rarely.
I don't smoke, like, all my money goes into that.
That's pretty much it.
Oh yeah, Jackie.
But Jackie's not really, uh...
She doesn't really cost much to maintain, you know?
Low maintenance.
I watch your stream while rushing on my deadlines.
Tell me if it's a crime.
No, that's cool.
Some people also just listen to it, or have it on a second monitor.
I think that's awesome.
I do the same thing when I watch streams sometimes.
I totally get that.
I'm happy to be secondary entertainment, you know?
Because that's what I do.
Dude, I love Create.
I think it's great so far.
I am just in awe of the skill that went into making that mod.
And the ideas behind it, like, the direction of it.
You know?
It really is...
Like a proper...
Almost standalone game quality.
You know?
It's just so good.
Even the small things, like...
Some of the textures they made for...
Some of the items could be completely...
You know...
You could think that Mojang made those, you know?
It is just so in line with the direction of the game.
It is beautiful.
It's great.
That's why...
When I first installed it, and I...
And I read, oh, I gotta install this JEI thing, right?
Okay, fine.
I'll do that.
So I logged in, I was like...
Just to test everything was working and all that before the first stream.
And I was like, what the hell is this?
This weird...
Bar on the right side that takes up, like, one-third of my screen.
And I see all the items from the get-go, and it's like...
It's looking like a debug menu, almost.
Like, what the hell is this?
Why?
And I was like, immediately, I gotta try and fix that.
I don't... I don't care how, I just wanna not see that, you know?
I feel like that's doing a disservice to create that is just so exceptional.
The best part of gaming in general...
Is to be transported away from reality.
Not that reality sucks...
Just that I like the gaming...
Worlds...
Quite a bit.
At least, that's how I got into World of Warcraft.
You know?
Transported you away from all the troubles of life, and...
You made cool new friends online that had the same interests, man.
World of Warcraft.
Vanilla.
Hmm.
That's the game.
What a game.
Just say reality sucks, bro.
The economy is not good.
I don't really feel impact of economy.
Not that much.
The only way I feel it is if cheese at the supermarket is...
Expensive or not, you know?
And right now it kinda is!
A little bit.
Especially minced meat.
That's why I haven't been eating that a lot.
That's why I'm eating poor man's chili.
Minced meat in Denmark right now is...
Freaking expensive for some reason.
I don't know what's happening.
Also, I am so happy I bought all my RAM...
And all my computer parts before all of this shit happened, you know?
RAM is so expensive now.
But right now I'm good.
I'm good for the foreseeable future, so I dodged that bullet.
Now I just hope my computer doesn't die.
Because then I'm in trouble.
I kept putting off upgrading PC and software.
I'm sorry to hear that.
That's unlucky.
My sister was in the same situation, you know?
She wanted to finally build a PC.
And she asked me, hey, you wanna help me build a PC?
Like, right when all of this went nuts, you know?
And I'm like...
It's a really bad time to build a PC.
Literally any other time in the last 20 years was great.
But right now...
Just right now, no.
Insane.
How expensive have laptops gotten though?
Paddle Dragon.
Is that also something that's gone up in price a lot?
I imagine it must have gone up because of mobile RAM and all that, you know?
I kinda hope AI bubble crashes soon.
Just to have it be over with, you know?
Because there's all this anticipation.
And I would love to put aside some money into like...
Some kind of index.
Stock index, you know?
Of a bunch of stocks.
Just to let it sit there for 10 years.
But I'm so afraid of putting it in now, right when everyone is talking about a bubble.
So...
Like, I don't know, man.
This may not be the time.
Right now might be the best time to buy for a good while though.
Yeah, I mean...
You could be right.
You could also be wrong, right?
That's the thing.
Nobody knows.
It's volatile.
Yeah, I heard something about the RAM companies having some sort of...
Oh, what is the name?
It's not a mafia, is it?
Like, they're definitely agreeing on a price and all hiking the price together.
There's a word for that.
What?
No, not Cabal.
Cartel, that's it.
Yes.
It's a cartel.
Those bastards.
Yep.
They know there's money to be earned, so they do it.
When will the VOD be uploaded?
Tonight.
Sometimes YouTube takes a while to upload though.
That's why it sometimes takes until the next day, because then I go to bed and it still isn't ready.
You know?
Most of the time though, it's ready quite fast.
Next stream, tomorrow or the day after.
I don't have a real-life work life right now.
I'm a full-time content creator.
Yeah?
I'm a full-time streamer right now.
And you know what?
It works out because I don't really have a lot of expenses.
Like I said before, you know, I don't really spend money on things, so I can actually get by just on this right now.
It's not extravagant by any means, but you know.
As long as I can pay for groceries and rent, I am like, over the moon.
That is like, insane.
And I also did save up a lot of money from my old job before I started this.
Just to have a buffer, you know?
Just in case a month was really bad or something like that.
So I have some money saved up, at least.
Best part about full-time streaming is to be able to decide your own schedule, for sure.
But it was actually a problem in the beginning for me.
Because I was so used to going to the office at a certain time, you know?
I had a purpose.
When you just wake up at home and you don't really have a schedule, it can really mess with your brain for a while.
Like, you're not used to that.
And I really do miss actually interacting with people more.
I would interact with people on a daily basis, right?
Nowadays, I live in a town that is, you know...
A little isolated, you could say, compared to when I was living in Copenhagen.
Not many people to talk to, and when I do have friends over, it's not as often, you know?
It's...
Yeah, I kind of miss that part.
How do you not have anxiety from all these people watching?
I don't know.
You get used to it, I guess.
Gotta fake the commute by going for a walk in the morning.
It's not a bad idea.
You know?
To have a schedule like that.
I thought about it.
Maybe I should do something like that.
But I probably wouldn't do it in the morning.
More like evening.
I like walking in the evening.
How do you rotate living in your walls?
What a sentence.
I hope not.
That's creepy.
Did your coworker ask why you left work?
Yeah!
I said, I'm going full-time streaming.
Wish me luck.
And they did.
They're like, good luck.
But in a nice way.
Not in a bad way.
Yeah, Jackie needs food.
Guys, I'm going.
I also need food.
So, it's chilly time.
Thank you for watching.
I'll see you in the next stream.
Either tomorrow or the day after.
Keep track of the Discord announcements- Not announcements, but Discord events.
And if I do decide to play it tomorrow or the day after, I will put it in an event on Twitch as well, if I remember.
So, yeah.
Have a good day.
I'll see you around.
Bye-bye.
And this is the second one.